(Sheldon:)Speaking of cowboys...
(Sheldon:)...do you know what country
has not one, but two cows on its flag?
(Sheldon:)The tiny landlocked nation of Andorra.
Ooh! The next classic episode
of Sheldon Cooper Presents:
Fun With Flags is writing itseIf.
(Howard:)Oh, let me try the voice recognition.
(Raj:)Hey, I let you peel the plastic,
don't get greedy.
- Hello?
WOMAN'S VOICE: Hello.
(Raj:)What's your name?
(Howard:)Look at that. There's finally a woman
in your life you can talk to.
(Raj:)Are you single?
(Siri:)I don't have a marital status,
if that's what you're asking.
(Raj:)Yeah, you're right, that's too personal.
We hardly know each other.
(Raj:)How about a cup of coffee?
I found six coffee shops.
(Siri:)Three of them are fairly close to you.